[The Unclouded Soul]
[Episode 22]
He's gone indeed.
He must've gotten injured when fighting
the Dreamshard Immortal,
which depleted all his power.
Everyone spread out and search carefully.
Capturing the Demon King
brings far greater merit
than catching thousands of minor demons.
Go!
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Yes!
Old crow.
You're back.
Why are they still alive?
Didn't you say you would kill them all,
turning them into living corpses
to be delivered to His Lordship?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Fine.
I'll take it as I didn't see anything.
Get to work quickly.
Remember,
don't beat them up too badly.
If their flesh and bones
stick to their clothes,
it'd be hard to sort out.
Wu Huan,
what's she talking about?
We're on the same side.
That's right. We're on the same side.
Let's take out that official first.
Wu Huan, help out!
You're just waiting to reap the benefits!
Go! Quick!
You!
Don't be too brutal!
Don't damage the heart!
Stir-fried human heart tastes the best!
You old demon!
I'm going to make you
into a stew!
Attack!
It was you
who tricked us...
I didn't trick you!
Well done, Wu Huan.
His Lordship will reward you greatly.
Wu Huan.
Nicely done.
Very well.
You'll all pay for this!
My Lord.
As for the rest,
let's turn them into barbecue.
Sounds good.
These Feiyu Guards
all have cultivation within them.
They are indeed
better than ordinary humans
for nourishment.
Without a scratch.
We've won.
My power is completely drained.
I'm starving.
My Lord, could you make something to eat?
Just this once.
You cannot steal them in the future.
Is your life
only worth a few bamboo shoots?
I wouldn't have saved you if I'd known.
You weren't the one who saved me.
It was His Lordship who saved me.
Right, My Lord?
Fine.
What has Heiwu been up to?
His Lordship is dead!
That's what Heiwu said.
The demon clan has no leader!
A new Monarch of All Demons
must be established.
Let's gather all great demons
to Demons' Valley
to select a new Demon King.
He lures all the demons over
to present them as gifts
to the Feiyu Guard, isn't he?
Where are they now?
Some have already been captured.
The rest of them
went into hiding in different places,
scattered all around.
I'll gather everyone right away
to follow My Lord to reclaim Youning Cave.
I'll go too.
I know where Xiaohu
and the Crane are hiding.
Let's go.
Don't be impulsive.
Since My Lord has returned,
there's no need to rush.
I-It
is urgent!
Is My Lord in no rush?
Heiwu,
although he betrayed the demons,
he is different from the human Feiyu Guard
and the human demon hunters.
If we fight to the death,
demons killing demons,
wouldn't that just amuse the humans?
So what should we do?
My Lord is back.
It's not our place to come up with plans.
Yes.
You rest and recover first.
I'll figure something out.
Go away.
You and an entire squad of Feiyu Guards
couldn't even handle this simple task?
My Lord.
Hong Ye has returned.
His power has increased greatly.
None of us are his match.
Hong Ye?
No wonder.
You've been through a lot.
So how did you make it back?
It was Hong Ye.
He asked me to deliver a message to you.
He said
he's willing to follow your advice
and won't be soft-hearted anymore.
He also said
for what we've done to the demons,
he'll make us pay back a thousandfold.
My Lord.
Should we move out of Youning Cave first
to lie low for a while?
Are you scared?
No.
Not with you here, My Lord.
He's already determined to kill.
What's the point of hiding?
Go to Pingjiang
and contact the Feiyu Guard.
Tell them Hong Ye has returned.
Ask them to send more experts immediately
to coordinate with us
from both inside and outside.
Go now!
Yes.
This is my only option
to save the demons.
Heiwu is different from Wu Huan.
He'll likely notice
you've lost your power.
So we need a foolproof plan
before confronting him.
I understand.
Don't even think about it.
Although I've lost my power now,
if I forcibly summon my demonic energy,
perhaps I could still—
No, you can't.
The most urgent matter now
is to eliminate Heiwu
and save the demons.
This is my only option.
Trust me,
this surely isn't the only way.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Let's think more.
Let's find Xiao Ming and Xiao Mu first.
Sure.
Heiwu is a coward by nature.
Before he figures out our true situation,
he won't make any rash moves.
He's probably on guard against us.
All right.
Too much worrying will give you wrinkles.
Then you'll truly become an old demon.
I won't allow that.
No.
Xiao Ming fears that there are mice
in Chengxiang Sea.
Luoluo!
Hurry!
Slow down.
It's not for you to eat.
Some are burnt, and some are cold.
Xiao Ming would be more upset than me
if he saw this.
It seems
we have to use our last resort.
That's all, right?
That's all.
All the catnip
from around here is right here.
Stop eating.
My Lord!
My...
My Lord.
Xiao Mu.
My Lord!
My...
I'm too ashamed to face My Lord.
You should...
Stand up first.
My Lord,
you're finally back!
We've been longing for your return,
My Lord.
Xiao Ming has missed you so much.
Heiwu told all the minor demons
that you were killed
by the Dreamshard Immortal.
But Xiao Ming didn't believe it.
I kept trying to sense you with my power,
but I couldn't feel anything.
I was completely out of options,
so I had to go to the human realm
and find a deity statue.
I made offerings
and prayed to it every day.
He's so noisy.
But it feels familiar.
My Lord, how are you?
Has the poison in your body been cured?
I'm fine.
Call Xiao Mu out.
All right.
My Lord.
Xiao Mu says
he failed to protect Demons' Valley
and was ambushed by Heiwu,
causing Youning Cave to be occupied.
He's too ashamed to face you.
I don't blame him.
I returned too late.
Let me talk with Xiao Mu.
My Lord.
It's all Xiao Mu's fault.
Now that you've returned,
let's go reclaim Youning Cave immediately.
I'm willing to die for this task.
This matter requires
careful consideration.
Xiao Ming is willing to risk his life too!
My Lord!
Your power...
Huh?
What?
Okay.
She said to clean up all traces here.
We'll meet
at the foot of the mountain later.
She said that much?
She also said you should eat all of these.
It's good for you.
Keep it up.
It's a lot.
Xiao Yao.
You're the jinx!
It's because of you
that My Lord is in this situation.
I've already told you.
I damaged my heart meridian
by using the Heart-Burning Incantation.
What does it have to do with Xiao Yao?
My Lord, stop defending Xiao Yao!
If it weren't for her,
why would you have gone
to the Realm of Mist and Void?
If you hadn't gone
to the Realm of Mist and Void,
how would you have ended up like this?
If you hadn't lost your power, My Lord,
how would I, no matter what,
be unable to sense your presence?
I once thought you had been...
The Dreamshard Immortal was after me
right from the start.
Even without Xiao Yao,
she would have used
other means against me.
You've been with me for so long.
You should know better than this.
My Lord.
Although the Heart-Burning Incantation
is an ancient spell,
judging by its name,
it only burns the heart,
not your power.
Perhaps your power, My Lord,
is just suppressed within your body.
It's possible!
What are you looking at?
I was just saying that to comfort you,
My Lord.
The ancient demons texts
are all sealed in Youning Cave.
If we reclaim Youning Cave,
we might find a solution.
But...
After you were attacked by Heiwu,
how much of your power remains?
Thirty percent.
But if I recover to 60 percent,
I can fight them to the death.
Life is precious.
Don't be so quick to risk your life.
You need to use this more.
Hey!
The technique turning leaves into silver—
can you still perform it?
I only need 10 percent
of my power for that spell.
Besides, at a time like this,
why are you...
why are you
still so obsessed with money?
Can't abandon my old trade after all.
Come take a look!
These are fine goods!
Come!
This is a divine weapon
for catching demons!
Have a look!
Xiao Yao.
The things they sell here,
as long as no one recites the spells,
we are safe.
Don't worry.
Remember,
you are...
Human.
Yes.
Let's go.
Sir,
which of your demon-catching items
works best?
Miss,
everything I sell
is of the highest quality.
But as for the best,
it would be
these demon-repelling fireworks.
You just need to pull it gently like this.
These two friends of mine
are afraid of fireworks.
Please continue.
Are you scared?
-No, I'm not.
-There's colorful poison with peach wood.
What happens if humans
accidentally inhale it?
Don't worry, miss.
This toxin is
our ancestral secret formula.
It only affects demons.
Humans won't be harmed by it.
As they say, it's good
for both offense and defense.
When ordinary demons encounter it,
they definitely can't handle it,
I assure you.
Is that all?
There's more.
But these fireworks are quite expensive.
I have more.
That's enough.
As long as they work well,
we'll take everything.
They work well, absolutely!
Miss, please wait a moment.
I'll get them from the warehouse for you.
Miss,
take a look at my treasure.
Have a look.
This gentleman.
I have some excellent items here.
Would you like to take a look?
Miss.
Look at this.
Look at this one.
This is a genuine peach wood sword.
All right, all right!
I got it!
One by one!
Qiankun Demon Subduing Pestle.
Cloud-Covering Ultimate Pill.
Nine Chain Lock.
Demon-Repelling Talisman.
Underworld Nineteen-Whip.
Body-Shattering Mirror.
So, Xiao Yao,
what exactly are you thinking?
You're planning to have My Lord
use these human demon-catching tools
against...
Heiwu.
Heiwu betrayed demons
and gave them to humans for torturing.
So we should let him have
a taste of human methods.
That makes sense.
My Lord, I won't comment on this for now.
But Xiao Yao, I would like to ask you:
do you think so little of Heiwu?
No matter what,
Heiwu is a great demon with
a thousand years of cultivation.
Do you think these cheap trinkets
can scare him?
Let me ask you.
What is Heiwu's true form?
I don't know.
An eagle, perhaps?
What eagle?
He's a horseshoe bat.
You've cultivated into a great demon,
yet you still love catnip,
don't you?
Heiwu is the same.
Some innate traits can never be changed.
These are specially prepared for him.
How are you going to set it up?
I need a group of friends to help.
A group of friends?
That's what happened.
So
Hong Ye's home
has been occupied by evil demons.
I'd like to ask for your help
to take back his home together.
Will you help?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Has the message been delivered?
It was sent 7 days ago.
Then why hasn't
the Feiyu Guard responded yet?
How about
I go check on it again?
That's Xiao Ming's voice.
Wasn't that cat severely injured?
How could it return so quickly?
You!
Go have a look quickly.
I...
My Lord.
Lord Heiwu.
Lord Heiwu!
My Lord, bad news.
Has Hong Ye returned?
Yes.
No, no.
As soon as I went out,
my eyes were blinded by toxic fog.
They must have ambushed me
and set traps.
I struggled greatly to fight my way out.
This is a human weapon.
Was it Hong Ye or humans who ambushed you?
I didn't see clearly.
My Lord.
Let's go.
There's...
What is this?
Who's there?
Hong Ye...
I got you.
My Lord,
it's me.
Me...
Heiwu.
Come and meet your death.
Come and
meet your death.
Meet...
Your death...
Death...
Death.
Hong Ye!
It's a new world in Demons' Valley!
You're no longer the Demon King!
I am.
Yes!
Get ready to appear.
Spread out evenly.
Careful!
Don't wobble.
Good, good.
Fly.
Hold steady!
Right here!
Don't move!
Let's go!
Retreat quickly! Go!
Why retreat?
Hong Ye is acting strange.
Go check what's happening.
Me?
Yes.
Do you think it should be me?
Go!
Do you know
how many birds die
under my cat claws every day?
Hong Ye!
I have the Feiyu Guard with me.
You're just one demon alone.
Stop putting on an act!
Come on!
To kill you,
I alone am enough.
Since you've removed yourself
from the demon registry,
then on behalf of all demons,
I'll end you.
Go.
Go, go.
Heiwu.
You are over.
It's fake.
You have no power left.
It's just an illusion.
All of it is fake!
I've already sent the Zhuyu herb back.
They'll keep their mouths shut.
Xiao Yao.
So?
Isn't my idea pretty good?
Yes.
Come on, praise me.
My Xiao Yao is so clever
and resourceful.
Oh, right.
I have a gift for you.
Close your eyes.
Close them.
Open them.
Congratulations on
reclaiming Demons' Valley, My Lord.
This is...
My Lord has been overthinking lately.
This jade comb
will refresh your mind and relieve stress.
Don't you like it?
I do.
My Lord.
Are you two discussing marriage now?
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm not talking nonsense.
According to human customs,
a comb is a symbol of marriage.
Don't take me for a fool.
Let's talk about important matters.
My Lord,
everyone knows you're back.
They're waiting outside
the cave entrance to see you.
It's all your fault.
It's all because of you.
You traitor.
Right.
You were the one
who came to Demons' Valley
to capture demons.
Let me tell you,
my father despises traitors like you.
It's all your fault.
You deserve this!
Look what trouble you've caused us.
You're terrible!
My Lord!
My Lord has returned!
You're finally back!
That's wonderful!
You're back.
You've returned.
That's great!
You're finally back!
My Lord.
-We missed you so much.
-We've been waiting for you for so long.
Yes, Wu Huan was terrible!
We missed you so much.
Enough.
My Lord has just returned.
Speak one at a time.
It was my fault.
During this time,
you all suffered because of me.
No, no, My Lord.
No rush.
You go first.
My Lord,
I heard your power has increased greatly.
Is that true?
Of course it's true.
My Lord, I heard that
in the Realm of Mist and Void,
you defeated Dreamshard.
Let me tell you all.
My Lord is the person
I admire most in my life.
Yes.
I admire His Lordship too.
Me too.
Exactly.
We all share the same sentiments.
My Lord is the most powerful.
Kitty, come here.
What's wrong?
Is Wu Huan's
true form a crow?
Isn't Wu Huan a crow?
Look at his beak.
And look at those talons.
This is a falcon.
The way you talk,
it's like
you're some kind of bird expert.
I come from a family of hunters.
An old bat managed to bewitch a falcon.
How interesting.
Let him down.
What?
Why?
Why should we let him down?
Let him down?
Do you know
how many demons
he has sacrificed to humans?
Those demons
suffered terrible torment.
That's right!
We can't let him go.
Exactly.
We can't let him down.
Right, we can't release him.
My Lord.
Last night, Heiwu abandoned Wu Huan
and fled alone.
Wu Huan now knows
his master's true nature.
Demons' Valley has
suffered repeated massacres.
Killing one more
would only be venting our anger.
Better to let Wu Huan
reflect on his actions.
Xiao Ming,
let him down.
My Lord.
Let him down.
Yes.
Listen to me, Wu Huan.
If you dare harbor any
evil thoughts about harming demons,
even if My Lord punishes me,
I will immediately,
at once,
kill you with my own hands.
-My Lord.
My Lord.
My Lord, please teach us.
-Please teach us.
-We can beat him up.
-Yeah.
-I can beat him up too.
Teach us new techniques.
-Please teach us.
-All right. Quiet.
If you have questions, ask me.
My Lord has taught me many techniques
on our journey.
I know them too.
My Lord worked through the night.
Don't disturb him.
Let him get some rest.
My Lord,
although during this time
we've all been running for our lives,
I'm the only one
who's been learning diligently.
The new technique
I've practiced is called Earth Escape.
Once I escape through it,
I travel a thousand miles in an instant.
No one can find me.
That's amazing!
Show it to us.
As for this Earth Escape Technique...
Go ahead.
Show us!
Come on!
Well...
Has Wu Huan done it yet?
Wu Huan hasn't done it.
You should do it.
I truly believe now
that reading too many books
isn't all that useful.
My Lord, you've read so extensively,
thinking you might learn something,
some way to deal with humans.
Who would have thought that you
would learn the Heart-Burning Incantation?
Isn't that basically suicide?
Besides,
who in their right mind
would develop such a technique?
We can't find any demons who've used
the Heart-Burning Incantation,
[Inside the Red Flame Fruit]
let alone any documented cases.
[is a hot liquid that makes it ripen
in a day.]
[Not only the color is bright,
it also has powerful fire.]
Who knows
if we can find a way to break the spell.
But anyway,
even if you're protecting Xiao Yao
in every way,
this has something to do with her.
My Lord,
where are you going now?
No one's watching over you anyway.
I don't even know
what you're so stubbornly clinging to.
So,
you reap what you sow.
Wh-Wh-What
a-a-are
you doing?
Luoluo.
My Lord.
Normally,
you should be feeling drowsy by now.
With My Lord back,
the entire demon realm is energized.
I can't be like before.
I must make myself useful.
You don't need to act like
you're too good to kill me.
Killing me to establish your authority
is inevitable.
Stop this hypocritical act.
I will ask you some questions.
Just answer me truthfully.
I once fell into a human trap,
and my mouth was caught
in a narrow-necked bottle.
Lord Heiwu saved me.
Though I've repaid the debt,
asking me to betray him
is impossible.
You certainly know how to repay kindness,
valuing loyalty above all.
But have you ever thought about
where those minor demons
who once honored you as their teacher,
and respected and loved you,
are now?
What exactly is going on
between Heiwu and the Feiyu Guard?
Stop wasting words, Hong Ye.
If you don't kill me today,
one day, I will kill you.
Do you hate me so much
that you would harm your own kind?
Hate is not the word.
Throughout history,
be it humans or demons,
when power shifts,
only when the previous ruler dies,
can the successor secure their position.
What if I lost my power
and posed no threat?
Would you still want to kill me?
Yes.
Why?
As long as you were once the Demon Lord,
you must be eliminated.
Water.
I want some water.
I'm not doing this
because I feel sorry for you.
Luoluo.
Could you
loosen this a bit?
I
can't breathe.
Just a little bit.
You betrayed our kind.
Why should I trust you?
Now that Hong Ye has returned,
and I'm in this state,
what could I possibly do?
Luoluo.
For the sake of our
teacher-student relationship,
and how we're both demons,
please?
Please, please.
Just a little.
Just a tiny bit, okay?
Fine.
I'll tie it back up.
You!
How could you trick me?
You're just too stupid.
Blame your own foolishness.
You think you can stop me?
Get out of my way.
You can't leave!
Luoluo.
I don't want to hurt you. Step aside.
Otherwise don't blame me for being rude.
My Lord said
demons must stand united.
I cannot let you go.
Another one
of Hong Ye's manipulative speeches.
You pig-headed fool.
My Lord.
It's fine.
You're injured.
As the mighty Demon Lord,
why shield a minor demon?
You once said,
only when the ruler dies,
can the successor become stable.
But in my view,
power
is granted only to those
who treat all beings equally.
Though we dislike humans,
they have a good saying:
"Heaven and Earth are not benevolent,
treating all beings as mutt dogs."
If the ruler
doesn't sincerely
and equally care for all demons,
how could there still be
a sanctuary like Demons' Valley?
How could Heiwu and us
still fight for power here?
You are good by nature.
Don't be misled by Heiwu anymore.
Xiao Yao.
Sit.
Why are you injured again?
I just scratched it by accident.
Where did you get it scratched?
In the bamboo grove.
You look very pale.
I haven't been
sleeping well these days.